[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sanskrit name of Mt. Everest is Devgiri.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Philip Bailey, Ronnie Laws, and Maurice White were members of what musical group?", "correct_answer": "Earth, Wind, and Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["The Temptations", "The Doobees", "INXS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the film version of Watchmen?", "correct_answer": "Zack Snyder", "incorrect_answers": ["Tim Burton", "Ralph Maccio", "Chris Nolan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a young eel called?", "correct_answer": "Elver", "incorrect_answers": ["Eeling", "Eelet", "Elvis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor was originally offered the role of Forrest Gump in Robert Zemeckis 1994 movie Forrest Gump?", "correct_answer": "John Travolta", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert De Niro", "Dustin Hoffman", "Sean Penn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animated film was produced by Steven Spielbergs Amblin Entertainment. The films main character became a mascot for UNICEF.", "correct_answer": "An American Tail", "incorrect_answers": ["Care Bears Movie", "The Great Mouse Detective", "The Adventures of the American Rabbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "GPRS is a new service designed for digital cellular networks.", "correct_answer": "General Packet Radio Service", "incorrect_answers": ["General Packet Radio System", "General Pocket Radio System", "Global Packet Radio Service"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Leonardo DiCaprios character in The Basketball Diaries (1995)?", "correct_answer": "Jim", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve", "John", "Jason"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a traditional Japanese low-alcoholic sweet drink?", "correct_answer": "Amazake", "incorrect_answers": ["Hojicha", "Kukicha", "Matcha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetable is used for the making of the popular Portuguese and Brazilian soup called Caldo verde?", "correct_answer": "Cabbage", "incorrect_answers": ["Tomato", "Vegetable marrow", "Eggplant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many people die in the final scene of Shakespeares Hamlet?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "0", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the inventor of the Malian peanut sheller?", "correct_answer": "Jock Brandis", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Edison", "George Washington Carver", "Ben Franklin"]}]